Register of the Vladimir Pribylovskiĭ collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Biographical sources for Russian politicians, 1989-2006
  - Rokhlin, Lev Iakovlevich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 21: 13)
  - Romanenko, Aleksandr Sakharovich, 1996 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - Romanov, Aleksei, 1997 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - Romanov, Anatolii Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - Romanov, Leonid Petrovich, 1992 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - Romanov, Petr Vasil'evich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - Romanovskii, Sergei Kalistratovich, 1992 (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - Romash, Aleksandr Vladimirovich, 1991 (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - Rossel', Eduard Ergartovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - Rostropovich, Mstislav Leopol'dovich, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Rozenbaum, Aleksandr Iakovlevich, 1993 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Rozov, Iurii Vladimirovich, 1995 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Rubinchik, Liubov' Borisovna, 1992 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Rudinshtein, Mark Grigor'evich, 1995 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Rumiantsev, Oleg Germanovich, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 21: 17)
  - Rushailo, Vladimir Borisovich, 1999 (Box-folder 21: 17)
  - Rutskoi, Aleksandr Vladimirovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 21: 18, Box-folder 22: 1-4)
  - Rybakova, Tamara Petrovna, 1995 (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Rybkin, Ivan Petrovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Rybnikov, Vladimir Anatol'evich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Ryzhkov, Nikolai Ivanovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Ryzhov, Iurii Alekseevich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Rzheshevskii, Oleg Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Saburov, Evgenii Fedorovich, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Sadovnichii, Viktor Antonovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Saenko, Gennadii Vasil'evich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Safonov, Anatolii Efimovich, 1995 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Safonov, Valentin, circa 1993 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Sagalaev, Eduard Mikhailovich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Saidov, Abdurashid Magomedovich, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Saidullaev, Malik, 1999 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Saikin, Valerii Timofeevich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Saltykov, Boris Georgievich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Sal'e, Marina Evgen'evna, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Saushkin, Evgenii Mikhailovich, 1992 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Savchenko, Iakov Evgen'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Savchenko, Oleg Vital'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Savel'ev, Andrei Nikolaevich, 1993 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Savitskaia, Svetlana Evgen'evna, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Savitskii, Valerii Mikhailovich, 1995 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Savitskii, Vitalii Dmitrievich, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Savost'ianov, Evgenii Vadimovich, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Sazonov, Nikolai Semenovich, circa 1990 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Sebentsov, Andrei Evgen'evich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - Sedykh-Bondarenko, Iurii Petrovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - Segen', Aleksandr, circa 1995 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - Seleznev, Gennadii Nikolaevich, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 22: 12)
  - Seleznev, Stanislav Vital'evich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Seliunin, Vasilii Illarionovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Semago, Vladimir Vladimirovich, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Semenenko, Petr Georgievich, 1996 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Semenov, Aleksandr Viktorovich, 1993 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - Semenov, Nikolai, 1995 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - Semenov, Viktor Aleksandrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - Semigin, Gennadii Iur'evich, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - Senderov, Valerii, 1992 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Sen'ko, Viacheslav, 1993 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Sergeev, Aleksandr Andreevich, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Sergeev, Aleksei Alekseevich, 1992 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Sergeev, Igor' Dmitrievich, 1999 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Sergeev, Valentin Mikhailovich, 1995 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Sergeeva, Ol'ga Olegovna, 1996 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Sergienko, Valerii Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Serov, Valerii Mikhailovich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Sevenard, Iurii, 1993 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Shabad, Anatolii Efimovich, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Shabalin, Ivan Petrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Shabanov, Aleksandr, 1996 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Shabdrasulov, Igor' Vladimirovich, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Shablinskii, Il'ia Grigor'evich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Shadaev, Damir Ravil'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Shafarevich, Igor' Rostislavovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Shafranik, Iurii Konstantinovich, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Shaimiev, Mintimer Sharipovich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - Shakhnazarov, Georgii Khosroevich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Shakhnovskii, Vasilii Savel'evich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Shakhrai, Sergei Mikhailovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 23: 5-6)
  - Shakkum, Martin Liutsianovich, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - Shamanov, Vladimir Anatol'evich, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - Shamiev, Igor' Borisovich, 1991 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Shamuzafarov, Anvar, 2000 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Shantsev, Valerii Pavlinovich, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Shaposhnikov, Evgenii Ivanovich, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 23: 9)
  - Sharapova, Arina Aianovna, 1999 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Shashurin, Sergei Petrovich, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Shatalin, Stanislav Sergeevich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Shatalov, Sergei Dmitrievich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Shatrov, Mikhail Filippovich, 1999 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Shchegolevskii, Mikhail Mironovich, circa 2000 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Shchekochikhin, Iurii Petrovich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Shchekochikhin, Viktor Vladimirovich, 1992 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Shchekotikhin, Evgenii Artem'evich, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Shchelkanov, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1992 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Shcherbakov, Viacheslav Nikolaevich, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Shcherbakov, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Shebarshin, Leonid Vladimirovich, 2000 (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Sheboldaev, Sergei Borisovich, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Sheinis, Viktor Leonidovich, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Shelov-Kovediaev, Fedor Vadimovich, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 23: 14)
  - Shenaev, Lev Sergeevich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 23: 14)
  - Shenderovich, Viktor Anatol'evich, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 23: 14)
  - Shenin, Oleg Semenovich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 23: 15)
  - Shepelev, Georgii Ivanovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 23: 15)
  - Shevardnadze, Eduard Amvrosievich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 23: 15)
  - Shevchenko, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1999 (Box-folder 23: 15)
  - Shevchuk, Iurii Iulianovich, 1993 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Shevelev, Grigorii Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Shimanov, Gennadii Mikhailovich, 1991 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Shishkarev, Vasilii Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Shmakov, Mikhail Viktorovich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Shmelev, Nikolai Petrovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 24: 2)
  - Shneider, Mikhail Iakovlevich, 1991 (Box-folder 24: 2)
  - Shoigu, Sergei Kuzhugetovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Sholokhov, Sergei, 1994 (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - Shorin, Vladimir Pavlovich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - Shostakovskii, Viacheslav Nikolaevich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - Shpigel', Leonid Teodorovich, 1994 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Shpitonkov, Vladislav Borisovich, 1995 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Shtil'mark, Aleksandr, 1996 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Shubin, Aleksandr Vladimirovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Shuikov, Valerii Averkievich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Shumeiko, Vladimir Filippovich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Shurygin, Vladislav Vladislavovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Shusharin, Dmitrii, 1993 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Shustov, Stanislav Pavlovich, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Shutov, Iurii Titovich, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Shvets, Liubov' Nikitichna, 1996 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Sidel'nikov, Andrei Iur'evich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 24: 9)
  - Sidorov, Evgenii Iur'evich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 24: 9)
  - Sigarev, Sergei Evgen'evich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 24: 10)
  - Silaev, Ivan Stepanovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 24: 10)
  - Simonenko, Petr Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 24: 10)
  - Simonov, Aleksei Kirillovich, 1996 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Simonov, Viacheslav Vladimirovich, 1999 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Siniavskii, Andrei Donatovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Sister, Vladimir Grigor'evich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Skliar, Gennadii Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 24: 12)
  - Skliarov, Ivan Petrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 24: 12)
  - Skokov, Iurii Vladimirovich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 24: 12)
  - Skorochkin, Sergei Grigor'evich, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Skuratov, Valerii Nikolaevich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Skurlatov, Valerii Ivanovich, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Skvortsov, Sergei Borisovich, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Slavin, Boris, 1996 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Sliva, Anatolii Iakovlevich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Slobodkin, Iurii Maksimovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Smitniagin, Leonid Viktorovich, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Smirnov, Aleksandr, 1996 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Smirnov, Andrei, 1993 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Smirnov, Boris Nikolaevich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Smirnov, Igor' Nikolaevich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Smirnov, Igor' Pavlovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 24: 15)
  - Smirnov, Il'ia, circa 1995 (Box-folder 24: 15)
  - Smirnov, Stanislav Alekseevich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 24: 15)
  - Smirnov, Vladimir Sergeevich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 24: 15)
  - Smolenskii, Aleksandr Pavlovich, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 24: 15)
  - Smolianoi, Artem Stanislavovich, 1992 (Box-folder 24: 16)
  - Smolin, Oleg Nikolaevich, 1999 (Box-folder 24: 16)
  - Sobakin, Evgenii Iur'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 24: 16)
  - Sobchak, Anatolii Aleksandrovich, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 24: 17-18)
  - Sobianin, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Sobianin, Sergei Semenovich, 1999 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Sokolov, Aleksandr Sergeevich, 1991 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Sokolov, Maksim Iur'evich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Sokolov, Veniamin Sergeevich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Sokolovskii, Viktor, 1994 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Soldatenkov, Gennadii, 1993 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Soloukhin, Vladimir Alekseevich, 1993 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Solovov, Viacheslav Mikhailovich, 1993 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Solov'ev, Sergei Aleksandrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Solov'eva, Valentina Ivanovna, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Soltaganov, Viacheslav Fedorovich, 1999 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr Isaevich, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 25: 3)
  - Sorokina, Svetlana Innokent'evna, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 25: 4)
  - Soros, George, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 25: 4)
  - Soskovets, Oleg Nikolaevich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 25: 5)
  - Sotnikov, Oleg Vasil'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Sotnikova, Gul'naz Ivanovna, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Stankevich, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 25: 7)
  - Stankevich, Zigmund Antonovich, 1999 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Stankov, Anatolii Georgievich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Starikov, Ivan, 2000 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Starkov, Vladislav Andreevich, 1992 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Starodubov, Vladimir, 1993 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Starodubtsev, Vasilii Aleksandrovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Starovoitov, Aleksandr Vladimirovich, 1997 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Starovoitova, Galina Vasil'evna, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 25: 9-10)
  - Stepankov, Valentin Georgievich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 25: 11)
  - Stepanov, Dmitrii, 1993 (Box-folder 25: 12)
  - Stepanov, Viktor Nikolaevich, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 25: 12)
  - Stepashin, Sergei Vadimovich, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 25: 13)
  - Stepovoi, Aleksandr, 1993 (Box-folder 25: 14)
  - Sterligov, Aleksandr Nikolaevich, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 25: 14)
  - Sterligov, German L'vovich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 25: 15)
  - Stoliarov, Aleksandr Grigor'evich, 1991 (Box-folder 25: 16)
  - Stoliarov, Nikolai Sergeevich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 25: 16)
  - Stolpovskikh, Viktor Stepanovich, 1998 (Box-folder 25: 16)
  - Stolypin, Vladimir Sergeevich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 25: 16)
  - Streletskii, Valerii Alekseevich, 1996 (Box-folder 25: 17)
  - Strelianyi, Anatolii, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 25: 17)
  - Strizh, Kseniia, 1999 (Box-folder 25: 17)
  - Stroev, Egor Semenovich, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Strugatskii, Boris Natanovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - Sulakshin, Stepan Stepanovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - Suleimenov, Ibragim, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Suleimenov, Olzhas Omarovich, 1994 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Sumin, Petr Ivanovich, 2000 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Surkov, Mikhail Semenovich, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Suvorov, Viktor Bogdanovich, 1999 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Svanidze, Nikolai Karlovich, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Sviridov, Andrei Aleksandrovich, 1992 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Sychev, Anatolii Pavlovich, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Syrovatko, Vitalii Grigor'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Sysuev, Oleg Nikolaevich, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Tarantsev, Aleksandr Petrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Tarasenko, Vasilii Georgievich, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Tarasov, Artem Mikhailovich, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Tarasov, Boris Vasil'evich, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Tarasov, Vladislav Mikhailovich, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Tarpishchev, Shamil' Anvarovich, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Teniakov, Eduard Veniaminovich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 26: 7)
  - Terekhov, Stanislav Nikolaevich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 26: 7)
  - Ter-Oganian, Avdei Stepanovich, 1999 (Box-folder 26: 7)
  - Tiazhlov, Anatolii Stepanovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 26: 8)
  - Tikhomirov, Aleksandr Nikolaevich, 1976-1995 (Box-folder 26: 8)
  - Tikhonov, Aleksandr Anatol'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Tikhonov, Georgii Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Tikhonov, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Timakov, Vladimir Viktorovich, 1992 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Timin, Sergei Aleksandrovich, circa 1990 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Timofeev, Lev Mikhailovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Tishkov, Valerii Aleksandrovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Titkin, Aleksandr Alekseevich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Titov, German Stepanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Titov, Konstantin Alekseevich, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Tiulenev, Andrei, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Tiurin, Aleksndr Nikolaevich, 1992 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Tkachenko, Aleksandr, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Tkachenko, Evgenii Viktorovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Tokhtakhunov, Alimzhan, 1999 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Tolboev, Magomed Omarovich, circa 1997 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Tolkachev, Oleg Mikhailovich, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Tolkachev, Valentin Iur'evich, 1994 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Tolstoi, Nikita Il'ich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Tomchin, Grigorii, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Toporov, Viktor, 1993 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Torkunov, Anatolii Vasil'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Tosunian, Garegin, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 12)
  - Travkin, Nikolai Il'ich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 26: 12)
  - Tret'iakov, Vitalii Tovievich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - Trofimov, Anatolii Vasil'evich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - Troitskii, Artem, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - Troshkin, Nikolai Nikitovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - Trube, Sergei Evgen'evich, 1991 (Box-folder 26: 14)
  - Trubin, Nikolai Semenovich, 1991 (Box-folder 26: 14)
  - Trubnikov, Viacheslav Ivanovich, 1996 (Box-folder 26: 14)
  - Tsagolov, Kim Makedonovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 26: 15)
  - Tsakh, Nikolai Petrovich, 1997 (Box-folder 26: 15)
  - Tsaregorodtsev, Aleksandr Dmitrievich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 26: 15)
  - Tsereteli, Zurab Konstantinovich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 26: 16)
  - Tsikaliuk, Sergei Andreevich, 1995 (Box-folder 26: 17)
  - Tsipko, Aleksandr Sergeevich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 26: 17)
  - Tsiuriupa, Aleksei Igorevich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 26: 17)
  - Tsoi, Sergei Petrovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 26: 18)
  - Tsoi, Valentin Evgen'evich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 26: 18)
  - Tsvetkov, Boris Mikhailovich, 1991 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Tsypliaev, Sergei Alekseevich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Tuleev, Aman Gumirovich, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 27: 2-3)
  - Tumanov, Vadim Ivanovich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - Tumanov, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - Tutov, Nikolai Dmitrievich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - Ubozhko, Lev Grigor'evich, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Ugrovatov, Vladimir Georgievich, 1992 (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Uliukaev, Aleksei Valentinovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Umalatova, Sazhi Zaindinovna, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Urazhtsev, Vitalii Georgievich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Urinson, Iakov Moiseevich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Urnov, Mark Iur'evich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Ursov, Iurii, 1996 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Usmanov, Alisher Burkhanovich, 1999 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Ustinov, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Utkin, Viktor Borisovich, 1996 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Utkin, Vladimir Petrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Uvarov, Boris Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Vainberg, Lev Iosifovich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - Vakhnina, Liudmila, 1996 (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - Vanin, Mikhail Valentinovich, 1999 (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - Varennikov, Valentin Ivanovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - Varov, Vladimir Konstantinovich, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Vartozarova, Liudmila Stepanova, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Vasil'ev, Dmitrii Dmitrievich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Vasil'ev, Dmitrii Valer'evich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Vasil'ev, Georgii Leonardovich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - Vasil'ev, Sergei Aleksandrovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - Vasil'eva, Larisa Nikolaevna, 1993 (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - Vavilov, Andrei Petrovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 27: 12)
  - Vedenkin, Aleksei Ivanovich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 27: 12)
  - Vedernikov, Eduard Valentinovich, 1992 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Vedernikov, Igor' L'vovich, circa 1990 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Velikhov, Evgenii Pavlovich, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Vengerovskii, Aleksandr Dmitrievich, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Verkhovskii, Aleksandr Mikhailovich, 1992 (Box-folder 27: 14)
  - Vershinin, Pavel Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 27: 14)
  - Verzhbitskii, Iaroslav Vladimirovich, 1993 (Box-folder 27: 14)
  - Veshniakov, Aleksandr Al'bertovich, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 27: 14)
  - Viakherev, Rem Ivanovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 27: 15)
  - Viatkin, German Platonovich, 1990 (Box-folder 27: 15)
  - Vidiapin, Vitalii Ivanovich, 1996 (Box-folder 27: 15)
  - Vid'manov, Viktor Mikhailovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Viktorov, Valer'ian Nikolaevich, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Vil'chek, Vsevolod Mikhailovich, 1995 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Vinogradov, Igor' Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Vinogradov, Nikolai Vladimirovich, 1997 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Vinogradov, Vladimir Viktorovich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Vinogradova, Irina Viktorovna, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Vishnevskii, Boris Lazarevich, 1999 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Vitebskii, Vitalii Iakovlevich, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Vitruk, Nikolai Vasil'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Vladislavov, Aleksandr Pavlovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 28: 2)
  - Vlasov, Aleksei Feliksovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 28: 3)
  - Vlasov, Iurii Petrovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 28: 3)
  - Vlasov, Iurii Vasil'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 28: 3)
  - Vlasov, Mikhail Aleksandrovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 28:: 4)
  - Voblikov, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1990 (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - Voinovich, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - Volchek, Galina Borisovna, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - Volkogonov, Dmitrii Antonovich, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 28: 5)
  - Volkov, Aleksandr Semenovich, 1995 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Volkov, Andrei Romanovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Volkov, Leonid Borisovich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Volkov, Nikolai Vasil'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Volkov, Viacheslav Vasil'evich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Volodin, Eduard Fedorovich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Volodin, Viacheslav Viktorovich, 1999 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Voloshin, Aleksandr Stal'evich, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Volovik, Aleksandr Mikhailovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Vol'skii, Arkadii Ivanovich, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 28: 8-9)
  - Vorob'ev, Aleksei, 1993 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Vorob'ev, Andrei Ivanovich, 1992 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Vorob'ev, Eduard Arkad'evich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Vorob'ev, Vasilii, 1996 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Vorogushin, Viktor Anatol'evich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Voronin, Gennadii, 1994 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Voronin, Iurii Mikhailovich, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Voronin, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 28: 11)
  - Voronov, Iurii Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 28: 12)
  - Vorontsov, Iulii Mikhailovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 28: 12)
  - Vorontsov, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 18: 12)
  - Vorotnikov, Vitalii Ivanovich, `, 1996 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Voshchanov, Pavel Igorevich, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 28: 13)
  - Vostokov, Vadim Iur'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 28: 13)
  - V'iugin, Oleg, 1999 (Box-folder 28: 13)
  - Zabelin, Sviatoslav Igorevich, 1993 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Zadonskii, Georgii Ivanovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Zadornov, Mikhail Mikhailovich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Zadornov, Mikhail Nikolaevich, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Zaikin, Anatolii, 1995 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Zaikov, Lev Nikolaevich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Zaitsev, Anatolii Aleksandrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Zaitsev, Viacheslav Mikhailovich, 1993 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Zakharov, Aleksandr Vladimirovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Zakharov, Aleksei Konstantinovich, 1996 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Zakharov, Mark Anatol'evich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Zakharov, Mikhail L'vovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Zakopyrin, Anatolii Nikolaevich, 1993 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Zalygin, Sergei Pavlovich, 1995 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Zamai, Boris Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Zamotin, Vadim, 1993 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Zapesotskii, Aleksandr Sergeevich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Zaslavskaia, Tat'iana Ivanovna, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 28: 16)
  - Zaslavskii, Il'ia Iosifovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 28: 16)
  - Zasurskii, Iasen Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 28: 16)
  - Zaveriukha, Aleksandr Kharlampievich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 28: 17)
  - Zavgaev, Doku Gapurovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 28: 17)
  - Zavidiia, Andrei Fedorovich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 28: 17)
  - Zharikov, Sergei, 1996 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Zharkov, Vladimir Mikhailovich, circa 1997 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Zharnikov, Aleksandr Evgen'evich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Zhenin, Vladimir Alekseevich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Zherbin, Nikita Fedorovich, 1993 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Zhigulin, Viktor Ivanovich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Zhikharev, Pavel Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Zhiliaeva, Nina Ivanovna, 1994 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Zhilin, Aleksandr Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Zhirinovskii, Vladimir Vol'fovich, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 29: 2-5)
  - Zhivilo, Mikhail, 2001 (Box-folder 29: 6)
  - Zhukov, Aleksandr Dmitrievich, 1999 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - Zhukov, Andrei Dmitrievich, 1994 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - Zhvanetskii, Mikhail Mikhailovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - Zimin, Dmitrii Borisovich, 1999 (Box-folder 29: 8)
  - Zimin, Sergei Gennad'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 29: 8)